<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <channel>

    <title>The Lincoln Repository: Creators matches any of "Hanheide,Marc", "Duckett,Tom", "Sklar,Elizabeth", "Saaj", "Elgeneidy", "Esfahani", "Bosilj", "Goher", "Calisti", "Das,Gautham", "Gao,Junfeng", "Ghafoor,Mubeen", "Maleki,Sepehr", "Al-Khafajiy", "Polydoros", "Galvez Trigo", "Millard,Alan", "Yue,Shigang", "Neumann,Gerhard", "Bellotto,Nicola", "Baxter,Paul", "Cielniak,Grzegorz", "Cuayahuitl,Heriberto", "Fox,Charles", "Kucukyilmaz,Ayse", "Parsons,Simon", "Pearson,Simon", "Bochtis", ",,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,". Results ordered -Date Deposited. </title>
    <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/</link>
    <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" href="http://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/cgi/search/archive/advanced/export_lincoln_RSS2.xml?screen=Search&amp;dataset=archive&amp;_action_export=1&amp;output=RSS2&amp;exp=0%7C1%7C-%7Ccreators_name%3Acreators_name%3AANY%3AIN%3A%22Hanheide%2C+Marc%22%2C+%22Duckett%2C+Tom%22%2C+%22Sklar%2C+Elizabeth%22%2C+%22Saaj%22%2C+%22Elgeneidy%22%2C+%22Esfahani%22%2C+%22Bosilj%22%2C+%22Goher%22%2C+%22Calisti%22%2C+%22Das%2C+Gautham%22%2C+%22Gao%2C+Junfeng%22%2C+%22Ghafoor%2C+Mubeen%22%2C+%22Maleki%2C+Sepehr%22%2C+%22Al-Khafajiy%22%2C+%22Polydoros%22%2C+%22Galvez+Trigo%22%2C+%22Millard%2C+Alan%22%2C+%22Yue%2C+Shigang%22%2C+%22Neumann%2C+Gerhard%22%2C+%22Bellotto%2C+Nicola%22%2C+%22Baxter%2C+Paul%22%2C+%22Cielniak%2C+Grzegorz%22%2C+%22Cuayahuitl%2C+Heriberto%22%2C+%22Fox%2C+Charles%22%2C+%22Kucukyilmaz%2C+Ayse%22%2C+%22Parsons%2C+Simon%22%2C+%22Pearson%2C+Simon%22%2C+%22Bochtis%22" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description></description><image>
        <url>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/images/sitelogo.png</url>
        <title>The Lincoln Repository: Creators matches any of "Hanheide,Marc", "Duckett,Tom", "Sklar,Elizabeth", "Saaj", "Elgeneidy", "Esfahani", "Bosilj", "Goher", "Calisti", "Das,Gautham", "Gao,Junfeng", "Ghafoor,Mubeen", "Maleki,Sepehr", "Al-Khafajiy", "Polydoros", "Galvez Trigo", "Millard,Alan", "Yue,Shigang", "Neumann,Gerhard", "Bellotto,Nicola", "Baxter,Paul", "Cielniak,Grzegorz", "Cuayahuitl,Heriberto", "Fox,Charles", "Kucukyilmaz,Ayse", "Parsons,Simon", "Pearson,Simon", "Bochtis", ",,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,". Results ordered -Date Deposited. </title>
        <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/</link></image>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 04:08:49 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 04:08:49 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright></copyright>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> An Agricultural Event Prediction Framework towards Anticipatory Scheduling of Robot Fleets: General Concepts and Case Studies </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49668/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49668/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Pal, Abhishesh, Das, Gautham, Hanheide, Marc, Leite, Antonio Candea and From, Pal  (2022) An Agricultural Event Prediction Framework towards Anticipatory Scheduling of Robot Fleets: General Concepts and Case Studies.  Agronomy, 12  (6).       ISSN 2073-4395  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> Effects of Wording and Gendered Voices on Acceptability of Voice Assistants in Future Autonomous Vehicles </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49118/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49118/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Jestin, Iris, Fischer, Joel E., Galvez Trigo, Maria J., Large, David R. and Burnett, Gary E.  (2022) Effects of Wording and Gendered Voices on Acceptability of Voice Assistants in Future Autonomous Vehicles.  In: CUI ’22: Conversational User Interfaces Conference, 26th-28th July 2022, Glasgow.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> In-Space Robotic Assembly and Servicing of High-Value Infrastructure </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49491/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49491/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Nair, Manu H., Saaj, Chakravarthini Mini, Esfahani, Amir G., Nanjangud, Angadh, Eckersley, Steve and Bianco, Paolo  (2020) In-Space Robotic Assembly and Servicing of High-Value Infrastructure.  In: 71st International Astronautical Congress, 12-16 October 2020, Dubai.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> Modelling and Control of an End-Over-End Walking Robot </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49496/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49496/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Nair, Manu H., Saaj, Mini and Esfahani, Amir G.  (2020) Modelling and Control of an End-Over-End Walking Robot.  In: 21st Towards Autonomous Robotic Systems Conference, 16 September 2020, University of Nottingham, UK.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Cloud SF – A continuous Integration Framework for the Design and Validation of Cyber-Physical Systems </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49494/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49494/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Bullegas, Gianmaria, Kapur, Anurag, Saaj, Mini, Nair, Manu H., Pop, Adrian and Fritzson, Peter  (2020) Cloud SF – A continuous Integration Framework for the Design and Validation of Cyber-Physical Systems.  In: Model Based Space Systems and Software Engineering MBSE2020, 28-29 September 2020, European Space Agency, Amsterdam.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Editorial: Robotic In-Situ Servicing, Assembly and Manufacturing </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49488/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49488/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Carignan, Craig R., Detry, Renaud, Rai Saaj, Mini, Marani, Giacomo and Vander Hook, Joshua D.  (2022) Editorial: Robotic In-Situ Servicing, Assembly and Manufacturing.  Frontiers in Robotics and AI, 9 .       ISSN 2296-9144  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Advances in Robotic In-Orbit Assembly of Large Aperture Space Telescopes </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49489/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49489/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Nair, Manu H., Saaj, Mini, Adlen, Sam, Esfahani, Amir G, and Eckersley, Steve  (2020) Advances in Robotic In-Orbit Assembly of Large Aperture Space Telescopes.  In: 15th International Symposium on Artificial Intelligence, Robotics and Automation in Space (i-SAIRAS 2020), 18-20 October 2020, Pasadena, US.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Robotics and Autonomous Systems for Net Zero Agriculture </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49460/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49460/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Pearson, Simon, Camacho‑Villa, Carolina, Valluru, Ravi, Oorbessy, Gaju, Rai, Mini, Gould, Iain, Brewer, Steve and Sklar, Elizabeth  (2022) Robotics and Autonomous Systems for Net Zero Agriculture.  AGRICULTURE ROBOTICS Current Robotics Reports, 3 .   pp. 57-64.      </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Using Semantic Systems Engineering Techniques to Verity the Large Aperture Space Telescope Mission – Current Status </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49463/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49463/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Gregory, Joe, Nair, Manu H., Bullegas, Gianmaria and Rai Saaj, Mini  (2022) Using Semantic Systems Engineering Techniques to Verity the Large Aperture Space Telescope Mission – Current Status.  In: Model Based Space Systems and Software Engineering MBSE2021, 29-30 September 2022, European Space Agency, Amsterdam.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Robotic crop row tracking around weeds using cereal-specific features </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49340/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49340/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Li, Xiaodong, Lloyd, Rob, Ward, Sarah, Cox, Jonathan, Coutts, Shaun and Fox, Charles  (2022) Robotic crop row tracking around weeds using cereal-specific features.  Computers and Electronics in Agriculture, 197 .       ISSN 0168-1699  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> Trustworthy UAV relationships: Applying the Schema Action World taxonomy to UAVs and UAV swarm operations </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49326/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49326/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Parnell, Katie J., Fischer, Joel, Clarck, Jed, Bodenman, Adrian, Galvez Trigo, Maria J., Brito, Mario P., Divband Soorati, Mohammad, Plant, Katherine and Ramchurn, Sarvapali  (2022) Trustworthy UAV relationships: Applying the Schema Action World taxonomy to UAVs and UAV swarm operations.  International Journal of Human–Computer Interaction .       ISSN 1044-7318  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Game Theory, Proxemics and Trust for Self-Driving Car Social Navigation </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49183/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49183/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Camara, Fanta and Fox, Charles  (2022) Game Theory, Proxemics and Trust for Self-Driving Car Social Navigation.  In: Social Robot Navigation: Advances and Evaluation (SEANavBench 2022), May 23rd-27th 2022, Philadelphia, PA, USA.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> RhythmTrain: making rhythmic sight reading training fun </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49153/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49153/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Godfrey, Reece, Rimmer, Matthew, Headleand, Chris and Fox, Charles  (2022) RhythmTrain: making rhythmic sight reading training fun.  In: International Computer Music Conference, 3-7 July 2022, Limerick, Ireland.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Towards Open Source Hardware Robotic Woodwind: an Internal Duct Flute Player </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49154/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49154/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Bennett, James, Moncur, Bethan, Fogarty, Kyle, Clawson, Garry and Fox, Charles  (2022) Towards Open Source Hardware Robotic Woodwind: an Internal Duct Flute Player.  In: International Computer Music Conference, 3-7 July 2022, Limerick, Ireland.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> The relationship of socio-demographic factors and patient attitudes to connected health technologies: a survey of stroke survivors. </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49216/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49216/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Drake, Archie, Sassoon, Isabel, Balatsoukas, Panos, Porat, Talya, Ashworth, Mark, Wright, Ellen, Curcin, Vasa, Chapman, Martin, Kokciyan, Nadin, Sanjay, Modgil, Sklar, Elizabeth and Parsons, Simon  (2022) The relationship of socio-demographic factors and patient attitudes to connected health technologies: a survey of stroke survivors.  Health Informatics Journal .       ISSN 1460-4582  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> Challenges for Multi-Agent Based Agricultural Workforce Management </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49036/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49036/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Harman, Helen and Sklar, Elizabeth I.  (2022) Challenges for Multi-Agent Based Agricultural Workforce Management.  In: The 23rd International Workshop on Multi-Agent-Based Simulation (MABS)).  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Temperature-based Collision Detection in Extreme Low Light Condition with Bio-inspired LGMD Neural Network </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49117/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49117/</guid>
  <type>conference_item</type>
  <description>  Zhang, Yicheng, Hu, Cheng, Liu, Mei, Luan, Hao, Lei, Fang, Cuayahuitl, Heriberto and Yue, Shigang  (2022) Temperature-based Collision Detection in Extreme Low Light Condition with Bio-inspired LGMD Neural Network.  In: 2021 2nd International Symposium on Automation, Information and Computing (ISAIC 2021), 03/12/21-06/12/21, Beijing.  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> A Looming Spatial Localization Neural Network Inspired by MLG1 Neurons in the Crab Neohelice </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49094/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49094/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Luan, Hao, Fu, Qingbing, Zhang, Yicheng, Hua, Mu, Chen, Shengyong and Yue, Shigang  (2022) A Looming Spatial Localization Neural Network Inspired by MLG1 Neurons in the Crab Neohelice.  Frontiers in Neuroscience .       ISSN 1662-4548  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <title> Artificial intelligence and ethics within the food sector: developing a common language for technology adoption across the supply chain </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49072/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49072/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Manning, Louise, Brewer, Steve, Craigon, Peter, Frey, P.J, Gutierrez, Anabel, Jacobs, Naomi, Kanza, Samantha, Munday, Samuel, Sacks, Justin and Pearson, Simon  (2022) Artificial intelligence and ethics within the food sector: developing a common language for technology adoption across the supply chain.  Trends in Food Science and Technology .       ISSN 0924-2244  </description></item>
<item>
  <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <title> Combined Free-Energy Calculation and Machine Learning Methods for Understanding Ligand Unbinding Kinetics </title>
  <link>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49062/</link>
  <guid>https://eprints.lincoln.ac.uk/id/eprint/49062/</guid>
  <type>article</type>
  <description>  Badaoui, Magd, Buigues, Pedro, Berta, Denes, Mandana, Guarav, Gu, Hankang, Földes, Tamás, Dickson, Callum, Hornak, Viktor, Kato, Mitsunori, Molteni, Carla, Parsons, Simon and Rosta, Edina  (2022) Combined Free-Energy Calculation and Machine Learning Methods for Understanding Ligand Unbinding Kinetics.  Journal of Chemical Theory and Computation, 18  (4).   pp. 2543-2555.     ISSN 1549-9618  </description></item>
    </channel>
</rss>
